adairs.com.au 2018-04-03

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

At Adairs, we recognise the importance of protecting your personal information. This is why we comply to a number of laws, including the Privacy Act (and Notifiable Data Breaches scheme under Part IIC of the Privacy Act 1988), this imposes regulations for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information, plus other matters including data quality and security, openness, access and correction. This document sets out our policy on the handling of personal information.

**Why do we collect personal information?**  
We are a specialist retailer of manchester and homewares, with stores around Australia and brands such as Adairs and Urban Home Republic.  
We collect, hold, use and disclose personal information to operate our business. This includes providing and improving our products and services, operating our customer programs such as Adairs Linen Lovers Club, maintaining and updating our records, communicating and managing our relationships with customers and other stakeholders, recruiting, training and managing staff, protecting our lawful interests and facilitating acquisitions and potential acquisitions of our business. For investors, we collect personal information to assess investment applications, manage your investment with us and provide investor services.  
We may not be able to do these things without your personal information. For example, we may not be able to communicate with you or fulfil your orders.  
We may provide marketing communications and targeted advertising to you on an ongoing basis by telephone, electronic messages (eg. email), online (including websites and mobile apps) and other means, unless you opt out or we are subject to legal restrictions. If you wish to opt out, please follow the instructions in the relevant marketing communication or contact us as set out below.

**What personal information do we collect?**  
The types of personal information we collect may include name, contact details, login credentials, payment details, purchase history and preferences and interests regarding our products and services. We also collect personal information about your dealings with us, including from records of any contact we have with you by telephone, email or online.  
If you are an investor, we also collect investment details. We collect some personal information under laws including the Income Tax Assessment Act and the Corporations Act.

**How do we collect personal information?**  
We may collect personal information about you in a number of ways including in-store, by telephone, post and email, through our website and social media, from public sources (including the Internet) and from third parties including those described below under ‘Who do we share personal information with?’.

**Who do we share personal information with?**  
We may exchange your personal information with our related bodies corporate, your organisation and representatives and with our service providers including providers of data storage, auditing, accounting, legal, business consulting, mail and delivery, customer contact, marketing, data processing, data analysis, document management, research, investigation, insurance, website and technology services. In relation to investors, we may also exchange personal information with our share registry and investor relations provider and we may be required by the Corporations Act to make certain investor details available to the public on request.

**Our website**  
If you visit adairs.com.au (our Website) to read, browse or download information, our system may record information such as your server address, top level domain (e.g. .com, .au, etc), date and time of your visit to the Website, pages accessed, information downloaded, previous site visited and browser type. This information is used for statistical, reporting and website administration and maintenance purposes.  
Like many other websites, our Website may use ‘cookies’ from time to time. A cookie is a piece of information that allows our system to identify and interact more effectively with your browser. The cookie helps us to maintain the continuity of your browsing session and remember your details and preferences when you return. You can configure your web browser software to reject cookies however some parts of our Website may not have full functionality in that case.  
When we send you emails or other electronic messages, we may record where you open the message and click on particular links. We may also record your interactions with our Website in these circumstances, as well as if you visit our Website after visiting another website which contains one of our advertisements. These processes help us to better understand what information is of interest to you.  
Our Website may use Google services such as Google Analytics from time to time. For more about how Google collects and processes data, and for opt-out instructions, please see Google’s privacy policy and their information at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.

**How do we store and secure personal information?**  
We implement a range of measures to protect the security of personal information, including – depending on the circumstances – firewalls, encryption, password protection, locked storage units and premises access restrictions. We hold personal information electronically and in hard copy form, both at our own premises and with the assistance of our service providers.   
Adairs Retail Group does not store any credit card details within the Adairs or Adairs Kids website databases. Pending payments are processed via eWay once authorised.  
All payments are processed via a 128bit SSL connection to eWay - Australia's leading payment gateway. For further security information on eWay you can visit their website www.eway.com.au

**How can you access and update your personal information?**  
It is your right under privacy law to ask for access to or updating of any of your personal information that may be held by us, except in some limited circumstances. Please see our contact details below. In many cases, we can assist you promptly and informally with these requests. In other cases, we may seek to verify your identity and ask you to make your request in writing.

**How can you contact us about privacy?**  
You can also contact us with any queries about privacy.   
Contact: Privacy Officer   
Phone: +61 (0) 3 8888 4500  
Mail: 2 International Court, Caribbean Business Park, Scoresby, VIC Australia 3179

If you raise any concerns about how we have handled your personal information, we may request additional details from you, and may need to engage or consult with other parties in order to investigate and deal with your issue. We will keep records of your request and any resolution.

For further information regarding the Privacy Act, visit the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner's website at www.oaic.gov.au.

Adairs Limited ABN 50 147 375 451  
Adairs Retail Group Pty Ltd ABN 29 128 287 776  
Last updated: 23/02/2018
